https://www.umassd.edu/privacy/

Skip to main content.
Email this pageEMAIL THIS PAGE
CLOSEUMassD125Mission and VisionAccreditationChancellor's OfficeAdministrationStrategic PlanUMassD MagazinePoints of DistinctionLocationDirectionsContactUMass SystemHelpVirtual Tour
Privacy Statement
UMass Dartmouth respects the privacy of visitors to its website to the extent permitted by United States, state and federal laws. This privacy statement informs you of what information is collected by this website and webpages with the domain "www.umassd.edu" and how the information is used. Other University of Massachusetts websites may adopt different privacy statements or policies.
Your use of websites is subject to the privacy statement of the providers of those websites. You are encouraged to be aware when you leave this website to read the privacy statement on each website you visit. You can tell you are leaving this website by looking at the URL of the destination site.
When you access the UMass Dartmouth home page "www.umassd.edu", and all pages within the website, your visit is not tracked by the University using your individual name or any other personal information. However, this website does utilize Google AdWords, Facebook, LinkedIn, and other software that may track and collect personal information from your device from the time you access our website. The information automatically collected is subject to their privacy policies.
Some computer information and automatic and optional information is collected by third party vendors, such as Google AdWords and Facebook when you access the website. This information is subject to the privacy policies of these services. Information collected may include: Internet domain and internet address of the computer, mobile device or other device you use to access the website.
Essential technical information collected includes the identification of the page or service you are requesting, type of browser and operating system you are using; and the date and time of access.
Optional information is collected only if you choose to send it. For example, if you choose to complete an online form, register for an event, or send an email. Optional information that is collected may include: Your name, email address, and the content of your email.
EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
This website is intended for general use and is viewable on the internet throughout the world. If you are visiting this website from the European Union (EU), personal information you provide to the University may not be subject to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). The GDPR replaces the Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC and was designed to strengthen data privacy protections for EU residents. Should you have additional questions or need information regarding GDPR’s impact and its application to personal information provided to the University, visit the GDPR website.
Terms and Conditions of Use
By using and/or accessing this website, signified by the URL "www.umassd.edu", you agree to these Terms of Use and Privacy Statement. This website is the official website of UMass Dartmouth. The website is owned and operated by UMass Dartmouth (referred to as "we" "us" or "our"). By using or accessing this website you agree that you have read these Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Statement and agree to be bound by and comply with them. If you do not agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Statement, please exit this website.
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of the Terms of Use and/or Privacy Statement at any time. Please review these Terms of Use and Privacy Statement periodically for changes.
Except as noted, the information below applies to the website, consisting of designated web pages or publications of the University, its departments, administrative offices, divisions, and other units pertaining to the website.
You may also find within the website publications created and maintained by UMass Dartmouth faculty, staff, students, student organizations and others for which the University is not responsible for the content and administration. These pages and their content, including but not limited to factual statements and opinions, are the sole responsibility of their creators and do not represent, explicitly or implicitly, positions, policies or opinions of UMass Dartmouth. Although UMass Dartmouth encourages compliance with all policies and practices at such websites, the University serves only as a provider of internet-related services in these cases.
Disclaimer of Warranty
While we try to maintain the information on the website as accurate as possible, we disclaim any warranty concerning its accuracy, timeliness and completeness, and any other warranty, express or implied, including warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.
Limitation of Liability
The user assumes all responsibility and risk for the use of this website and the internet in general. Under no circumstances shall UMass Dartmouth, its employees, Chancellor, Trustees, agents, representatives, affiliates, or anyone involved in creating or maintaining this website be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages, lost profits, or other damages whatsoever including, without limitation, damages that result from; the use or inability to use or access to the website and/or any other websites which are linked to this website; reliance by a visitor on any information obtained via the website; or mistakes, omissions, interruptions, deletion of files, viruses, errors, defects, or any failure of performance, communications failure, theft, destruction or unauthorized access. In states which do not allow the above limitations of liability, liability shall be limited to the greatest extent permitted by law.
Copyright and Acceptable Use
All text, images, graphics, logos and information contained on the website is the intellectual property of UMass Dartmouth, unless otherwise identified. You must obtain written permission in order to reproduce, distribute, perform, display, or license a given work. Whether or not a website includes a statement about copyright, the U.S. copyright act provides protection for such works, and they may not be used or reproduced without permission.
UMass Dartmouth is not responsible for any errors in the material provided on the website and shall not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of any material found at this website or on any other website with the "www.umassd.edu" domain. Links may be directed to these pages, but images, logos, maps, may not be copied and/or posted for any reason.
Logos, Designs, and Trademarks
Certain names, words, titles, phrases, logos, icons, graphics or designs appearing in the pages of this website may constitute registered or unregistered trademarks or trade names of UMass Dartmouth. The display of any of the above trademarks or trade names on pages of this website does not imply that any license has been granted to any third party to use the trademarks or trade names of UMass Dartmouth.
Cookies and Web Beacons
The website utilizes "cookies" to enhance your experience on this website and for marketing purposes. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's, mobile device’s, tablet’s or other device’s browser to help us improve our access to our website and identify repeat visitors to our website. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of visitors to our website to enhance the experience on our website. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our website. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services, or to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. In addition, we may use the services of third parties to collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements. Cookies do not store personal information about you, unless you voluntarily provide it. UMass Dartmouth does not collect any personal information about you unless you provide that information voluntarily by sending an e-mail, completing an UMass Dartmouth Information Request Form, or completing an online application.
You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. Your browser may also be set not to accept cookies.
UMass Dartmouth may collect a limited set of non-personal information about you to help manage our online advertising and promotions, we or our third party advertising providers use "web beacons" (also known as "clear gifs" and "pixel tags"), in conjunction with cookies as non-personal information. Web beacons are small transparent graphic images used by many websites in connection with cookies. For more information about the use of this technology by us and our third-party advertising service providers, including how to opt out of these technologies, please visit the Consumer Opt Out page on Network Advertising Initiative and Adobe Digital Marketing Suite Opt Out page.
UMass Dartmouth may use remarketing pixels created by Google AdWords, DoubleClick, LinkedIn, Facebook, or other services to show you ads or relevant content on these channels or across the Internet. These marketing pixels collect information about the websites you visit, which are stored by these services and then provides you ads on other websites. You may manually opt out of these services or the vendor’s use of cookies by visiting their websites. Here are how to opt out of third-party services that may or may not be utilized on this website:
Google Ad Settings
Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page
DoubleClick opt-out page
Social Media Features
Our website includes social media functions, including Facebook buttons, and widgets, developed and maintained by UMass Dartmouth-approved vendors and/or third-party services. These features may collect your IP address, pages you visited, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our websites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Computer Information Technology Services (CITS)
UMass Dartmouth Computer Information Technology Services (CITS) establishes, monitors and enforces policies for use of UMass Dartmouth computing and information technology resources which include, but are not limited to, equipment, software, networks, data, and telephones whether owned, leased, or otherwise provided.
Links to Other Sites
This website contains links to other websites. This website is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave this website to read the privacy statements of other websites.
Updates to the Terms and Conditions and/or the Privacy Statement
UMass Dartmouth has the right to make changes or additions to the Terms and Conditions of Use and/or the Privacy Statement at any time. Please review the Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Statement periodically for changes.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about the Terms and Conditions of Use or the Privacy Statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website, please contact UMass Dartmouth University Marketing Web Development.
The Privacy Statement and Terms of Conditions of Use was last updated on May 30, 2019.
Last modified: Thu, May 30, 2019, 04:28 by Hillary Sylvia
CLOSE MAIN MENUCheck My StatusmyUMassDSupport UMassDDirectoryReturning to Campus
AboutAdmissionsAcademicsResearchOutreachStudent LifeAthleticsAlumni & Friends
Current StudentsmyUMassD is our web portal, a central location for email, notifications, services, and COIN: Corsairs Online Information.
Log inAcademic CalendarAcademic Resource CenterCampus MapCampus StoreCareer CenterCommencementCorsairs CareCounseling CenterCourse CatalogDisability Services: Access & SuccessFinancial AidHealth ServicesHousing & Residential EducationInternational Student & Scholar CenterLibrarymyAlert Emergency AlertsParkingPoliceRegistrarSAIL: Student Activities, Leadership & InvolvementSexual Violence AwarenessStudent EmploymentStudy AbroadTechnology/New StudentsTransportationMore Student LinksProspective StudentsAcademic ProgramsAccepted! Next StepsAlternate Admissions: College Now/STARTApplyCourse CatalogFast FactsFinancial AidInternational StudentsLife on CampusParents GuideRequest InfoTransfer StudentsTuition & FeesUndergraduateVeteransVisitGraduate StudiesApplyDeadlinesInternational StudentsMasters, Doctoral & Certificate ProgramsRequest InfoCourse CatalogUMass LawApplyRequest InfoOnline & Continuing EdApplyRequest InfoUndergraduate, Graduate & Certificate Programs
Support StudentsNewsEventsCampus MapDirectionsmyUMassDSupport UMassDDirectoryCheck My Status
bg
Visit us virtually
Visit us from anywhere, at any time.
Take a virtual tour of the UMass Dartmouth campus.
+t4
